what up Twitter
sometimes forget to click the Twitter
woman oh good art we got people joining
that's good
um yeah where my red white blue maverick
hoodie today in honor of America guys
know I'm from America I love America
America is a great country cuz we have
freedom we have we have First Amendment
Alex are you telling me America's
terrible I love America I love America
and that's why I'm wearing my red white
and blue
maverick hoodie the great thing about
America is you don't have to love the
government you don't have to love the
people but you have to love America I
don't know what it is but just sounds
good you'd never say that don't ever
America has has has provided me with
with so much this tree see this tree
it's part of America okay okay so that's
that's honestly you guys always take for
hugs I swear I'm not on drugs today but
we are here to show new friends ah maybe
I'm a little biased because I live in
America I think everybody should feel
that way about about their country you
could say you look at the greatest
country and I'll agree with you probably
except as long as it's America yeah new
car
America we are going to talk about our
new car it is a Honda Accord 2.0 touring
oh yeah check it out Accord 2.0 touring
look at that oh yeah they detail at
night I'm a little bit dirty
yeah alright um so let's go for a ride
let's see what we got here see is the
key I don't know where the other key is
how much well we traded in the Ford
Fusion so the Ford is gone it is not the
year of the for the year the Ford is
cancelled do I like it
I liked the Ford better to be honest I'm
an honest person
all right just drive that a time on yes
I only metaphorically always white white
is nice it's got this kind of shifter ya
know the car dealers don't ask too many
questions
it reminds me a little of the white
Acura
wait why won't it rev sport
where's this crap okay well so it's got
some like limiter or something I guess
it kind of makes sense cuz I'm in park
um I think it has a hard I don't know if
you guys can see it yeah check out the
hide these things are kind of stupid but
at least you could turn it off no no
nope the ILX is still over there you
could see it oh yeah ball so hard that's
right
let's see what else we got in here okay
here's the window sticker so it comes
with all this great shit Honda sensing
so up here we have the camera with the
Bosch system so we're gonna build open
pilot support for the Bosch system got a
skylight up here pretty nice traffic
sign recognition on the hide absolutely
so let's put this away we'll go for a
little Drive just a little too much
look at that 17 miles
poor supercruise - acura we can pour it
supercruise - this car baby oh yeah
stick turning radius it really like when
you view this thing as a sports car and
not at like a luxury sedan you enjoy it
a lot more pretty cool guys this is a
Honda Accord 2.0 liter touring the
top-of-the-line Honda Accord and we're
gonna support open pilot it has bosch so
we'll probably be releasing our first
reflash of the bosch radar oh man now
this car does make you want to raise
people
oh yeah
all right that's pretty fun guys but
yeah so hello to our brand new Honda
Coors got a backup cameras pretty decent
all right you know what you scope is can
see this yeah the Ford didn't work out
oh yeah oh that felt nice oh there is
self racing cars um let's see what we
can do here what's this oh look it'll do
the projection to straight down that's
pretty cool let's do a review of this
thing is it any good
parking brake electronic parking brake
who trust these things we got econ we
got sport we got I like these shifters
and they're pretty nice yeah that's
right it's not so nice oh I can hack it
we got Lane Keeping Assist
we got the following distance button
we'll be sure to disable that really
soon volume on the thing no I just drew
some GM's yesterday I kind of like this
LCD like that
[Music]
in City of Compton oh look at that
seismometer oh that's pretty nice we oh
yeah yeah look at that's a nice view
actually what's red line just a sports
car man
I really it makes you want to go right
next tight steering wheel but yeah no
we're going to uh hit sport on tack mode
it switches I let's try Oh what is that
is that like boost pressure or something
oh it's turbo pressure oh that's so cool
no no no this is not a CVT it's a
ten-speed it's a ten speed dual clutch
I think it's dual clutch I didn't feel
shifting lag at all yeah so this is
absolutely not a CVT this actually has
the same engine as the Civic type-r just
a detuned variant of it kind of cool too
I wonder if you can reflash it and get
the Civic Type four arms they claim it's
a claim it's I don't know like but ya
know it's the same engine block that's
the same type are not dual clutch this
week do a test drive we always do test
drives let's close that up
cool scope ease so there's our new
friend bond cord touring we're gonna be
adding support for it to open pilot so
we're also gonna be hopefully selling a
Honda Bosch giraffe eventually so you
guys will know what the new product
announcement is when I say new product
announcements alright thank you for
watching
welcome to the future and the future is
Honda and Toyota it is the year of the
Honda and the Toyota and it will be the
year of a Honda Toyota next year to give
us Honda and Toyota are the future so
far log-on Toyota today make sure to go
shop now comment on the I get your Yan
and Panda and giraffe and install the
great - camps offer focus that's right
brevin to anybody who watches me not
focus uh
you gotta tell me George you gotta focus
right yesterday almost bought of GM and
nobody in the company was like George
why you're buying a GM you got to focus
people were supportive can't do that
your scope these know us up
remind me focus because we're gonna be
supporting what cards we're gonna be
supporting us
or cars who knows six cars who can name
them all ten minutes ten minutes go
that's good I like the new I like to do
format
well guess one good grandpa nacelle left
it alas go P nope now Subaru is eyes not
on the list that's right to be removed
by dealer Oh take the airbags out just
the sticker that's right Honda and
Toyota I'm a big Jesus man love Jesus
but also love the Honda CRV the Honda
Civic the Honda Accord the rav4 the
Corolla it may be the Camry maybe the
Kaveri
maybe not the Camry I don't know you're
my friend - Lord Trenton everybody's my
friend who's not my friend who's not my
friend I don't know I don't know man I
like what Yvonne's been doing lately I
like what I like what oh yeah I know
your chase I know sob my name - printer
after you I like what Ilan has been
doing lately Pravda bro it's it's it's
really it's so unfair the way the media
attacks them for some of this stuff love
woody Long's doing a lot is a bro bro
army loving that stuff no is he in a
midlife dude that's what I said him this
morning in my tweet
it's not about ideas everybody can come
up with why don't we have a rocket that
shoots up and lands yeah easy idea now
implement it and make it a profitable
company that's where the skill comes um
you are describing reddit in a weird way
yes one of the problems even hacker news
even hacker news they frequently linked
to to journalism sites right um I have
an idea that this is like a few
reporters who are particularly bad I'd
love to see like reporters track records
on whether they basically like a factual
t-score and a clickbait eNOS score um I
think would be cool I'm very excited to
sign up for Pravda or whatever whatever
it's gonna be
I don't do it but I don't think it's
good idea execution is key it really
comes down to execution and that's what
this
that's of every startup is like if they
could think about like like uber Airbnb
right Oh what if we like people drive
each other around
yeah easy idea now execute on it people
give out their house yeah easy idea what
it was like a box you could type
anything in and it would give you the
answer yeah that's Google right do i do
have Tesla stock I almost bought GM
stock yesterday I am hyped on GM but I
didn't didn't buy any GM stock good
thing I didn't ever by Ford stock Ford
stock is uh it's like the monkeys from
the e-trade commercial before they flip
that chart so that is what is going on I
sound so that's straight I think that as
a compliment I like that
sometimes I like the way I sound when I
talk usually not on the scope ease
but yeah what's up um so that's that
this is my new friend it's a Honda
Accord Tesla Auto correlation I don't
know what that means it's Auto
correlation auto car later happy guy the
common tree is not cut down we still
absolutely have a commentary of
commentary and a comment three are we
don't talk with that alright cool thanks
go peace
bye-bye blockchain we love blockchain
bye-bye